## KAPIL CHAVDA

**C:** 7359401664

C 201 Silver Residency, Kathwada Road

Opp Saint Xavier's School, Nava Naroda, Ahmedabad Gujarat

kapilchavda28@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Associate with a Growth oriented organization with determination, dedication and discipline; deploy my Competencies towards personal and professional growth.

Motivated customer service specialist with over 2.6 years retail experience in a fast-paced, team-based environment.

Excelling at customer satisfaction and retention. Flexible and hardworking in deadline-driven environments.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

DOB: 28-01-1991Sex: Male

Nationality : IndianReligion : HinduMarital Status: Married

**SKILLS** 

Quick learner

**Exceptional Communication Skills** 

Cash Flow management

Hard Working

**INTERESTS** 

- Cricket
- Gaming
- Reading Chess
- Internet

**WORK HISTORY** 

Branch Service and Operations Manager: DCB Bank Limited

Bareja Branch, Bareja, Ahmedabad 382425 Gujarat Oct 2021 to Current

Teller Service Executive: DCB Bank Limited

Relief Road Branch Ahmedabad, Gujarat March 2018 to Oct 2021

Customer Relationship officer • Bharti Airtel Limited

Ahmedabad, Gujarat • July 2015 to Feb 2018

- Greeted customers entering the store to ascertain what each customer wanted or needed. Trained new cashiers on procedures,
- customer service and sales techniques.
- Received customer payments.
- Operated a cash register for cash, check and credit card transactions with 100% accuracy..
- To Maintain Daily Cash Report and Coordinate with Circle and Central Finance Own-store team on Daily Basis

**LANGUAGES** 

**Customer Service Agent** • *NJ India Invest Private Limited* Ahmedabad, Gujarat • January 2014 to March 2014

**EDUCATION** 

English, Hindi, Gujarati

10th - English • Shree Siddharth High School

Keshod • 2006

**12th** - Commerce • Apurv Vidhyalay

Dhoraji • 2008

**B.Com** - Commerce • *J K M Commerce* and BBA College

Junagadh • 2011

**PGDCA** - Computer Programming • Patel *Kelavani Mandal College of Technology*Junagadh • 2012

**MBA** - Finance • L *J Institute of Engineering And Technology* Ahmadabad • pursuing

ADDITIONAL CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- I have 2 months experience with N J India Invest Pvt. Ltd and did market study on AWARENESS OF MUTUAL FUND AMONG LIFE INSURANCE & SMALL SAVING AGENTS.
- Participated in Business Management Model (Prepaid Meter generate electricity) at L J Institute of Management studies 2014
- Participated in HR EXCELLENCE SERIES at L J Institute of Management studies 2013
- Participated in NATIONAL DAY CELEBRATION at Gujarat Technological University 2015

I Hereby Affirm that the above Information is True to the best of My Knowledge	
Kapil Chavda	Date